rocketlawyer.com 2016-06-09

# Rocket Lawyer Privacy Policy

Last Updated: 2/17/2016

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Privacy Policy governs data collection and usage of the products, services, software, platform and websites (collectively, "Services") provided by Rocket Lawyer Incorporated and any of our affiliates (collectively, "Rocket Lawyer"). By using the Services, you consent to the data practices described in this policy as well as our Terms of Service. If you do not agree to any part of this Privacy Policy, then you should stop accessing the Services.  

## Collection of your Personal Information

Rocket Lawyer may collect personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, physical address or telephone number. If you purchase our Services, we will collect and store your billing and credit card information. Rocket Lawyer may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your Postal Code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. Rocket Lawyer will not delete customer information for paying members. However, Rocket Lawyer reserves the right to delete customer information for members with a free account status at any time.

Information about your computer hardware and software also may be automatically collected by Rocket Lawyer. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Rocket Lawyer for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Services.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Services, this information may be collected and used by others.  Rocket Lawyer encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from our website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Rocket Lawyer is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the websites we operate.

Back to Top

## Use of your Personal Information

Rocket Lawyer collects and uses your personal information to operate our websites and deliver the Services you have requested. Rocket Lawyer may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Rocket Lawyer and its affiliates. Rocket Lawyer may also contact you to participate in surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Rocket Lawyer does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Rocket Lawyer may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party without your express consent. In addition, Rocket Lawyer may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Rocket Lawyer may share your information with third parties who perform tasks required to complete a purchase transaction. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these Services, and they are obligated to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Rocket Lawyer keeps track of the pages our customers visit within our websites in order to determine what Services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the websites we operate to users whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. Rocket Lawyer uses tracking pixels to collect information that helps us provide our Service to you. Please note that any "do not track" signals sent by your web browser or other mechanism have no effect on the collection of personally identifiable information by Rocket Lawyer. In addition, other parties who perform data analytics for Rocket Lawyer, such as Google Analytics, may collect personally identifiable information about your online activities when you use our Services. Third party affiliates of Rocket Lawyer may have different policies with respect to "do not track" signals and Rocket Lawyer makes no representations with respect to such policies.

Rocket Lawyer uses tracking to create remarketing audiences of users based on user behavior/their visits to our website. Rocket Lawyer may also target these users with custom ads based on affinities/interests, geographic and demographic signals. Rocket Lawyer only shares browser-level data through third party vendor tracking such as Google Analytics. Users can opt out of these advertising features by visiting Google or resources like the NAI consumer opt-out page. Rocket Lawyer may use email addresses to target users with custom ads through 3rd party advertising platforms. Rocket Lawyer shares customer information with third parties to perform services (advertising) on our behalf. 

Rocket Lawyer may disclose personal information when we are required to or we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this Privacy Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety; to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of the Services; or if we believe that an emergency involving the danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires or justifies disclosure of personal information.

Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information could be transferred to third parties as one of Rocket Lawyer's business assets. In such an event, we will attempt to notify you before your personal information is transferred, but you may not have the right to opt out of any such transfer. 

Back to Top

## Communications with Attorneys

In order to ensure delivery of Services and for quality assurance purposes, Rocket Lawyer will have access to communications with attorneys which are transmitted through the Services (such as the Ask a Lawyer service). As a result, if you choose to communicate with an attorney through the Services, please note that any such communications between you and a participating attorney may not necessarily be treated as confidential information by the attorney or protected by the attorney-client privilege doctrine. For additional information, please read the section in our Terms of Service entitled Interactions with Attorneys on Rocket Lawyer. 

Back to Top

## Use of Cookies

Our website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you register an account with Rocket Lawyer, a cookie helps us recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to our website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Services.

Back to Top

## Security of your Personal Information

You are responsible for safeguarding and preventing unauthorized access to the user information and password that you use to access our Services. You agree not to disclose your password to any third party and you are responsible for any activity using your account, whether or not you authorized that activity. Please immediately notify Rocket Lawyer of any unauthorized use of your account.

Rocket Lawyer secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. In addition, Rocket Lawyer secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Back to Top

## Children Under Thirteen

Our Services are not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and such use is prohibited by our Terms of Service. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you become aware that a child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

Back to Top

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Rocket Lawyer may change the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time, and will always post the most up-to-date version on our website.

Back to Top

## Contact Information

Rocket Lawyer welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. Please Contact Us. 

For more information, please review our Terms of Service and FAQ section. 

Back to Top
